Hello. I am Stephen Wavers, president of the Federation of
European Fire Officers, a network representing fire service
leaders in the 24 European countries.
As FEU president, I am delighted to offer our support for
this new European campaign, namely European Smoke Alarm
Day. It's a great addition to the programme of events
organised for European Fire Safety Week,
and is a very worthwhile campaign which help to save lives
all over Europe.
And this campaign, organised by the European Fire Safety
Alliance, has the potential to directly impact the lives of
500 million citizens in Europe.
And this campaign is in keeping with the aims of the FEU,
namely, the improvement of fire safety awareness and
sharing the best of practice within European member states.
So I would like to congratulate everyone involved in
organising this campaign, and I can assure you that we will
do everything we can as fire service around Europe,
to encourage more citizens to install smoke alarms in their
homes. So I encourage our fire service colleagues around
Europe to support this campaign and help to make it a
success. And it's very important because smoke alarms saves
lives. So do it.